1m2alt Berk Alt
1m2[37] This Is Berk
***1m6[10] Anybody See That
**1m6[10] Anybody See That
*1m6[10] Anybody See That
1m6[10] Anybody See That
***1m7a War Room
**1m7a War Room
*1m7a War Room
1m7a War Room
***1m7b-c[13] Training Out There
**1m7b-c[13] Training Out There
*1m7b-c[13] Training Out There
1m7b-c[13] Training Out There
***2m8 Hiccup Comes Home
**2m8 Hiccup Comes Home
*2m8 Hiccup Comes Home
2m8 Hiccup Comes Home
***2m9 Dragon Training
**2m9 Dragon Training
*2m9 Dragon Training
2m9 Dragon Training
***2m10 Wounded
**2m10 Wounded
*2m10 Wounded
2m10 Wounded
***2m11 The Dragon Book
**2m11 The Dragon Book
*2m11 The Dragon Book
2m11 The Dragon Book
***2m12 Hiccup Focus
**2m12 Hiccup Focus
*2m12 Hiccup Focus
2m12 Hiccup Focus
2m13 Offering
***2m14 Forbidden Friendship
**2m14 Forbidden Friendship
*2m14 Forbidden Friendship
2m14 Forbidden Friendship
***2m15 New Tail
**2m15 New Tail
*2m15 New Tail
2m15 New Tail
***3m16 Teamwork
**3m16 Teamwork
*3m16 Teamwork
3m16 Teamwork
***3m17 Charming The Pziiffelback
**3m17 Charming The Pziiffelback
*3m17 Charming The Pziiffelback
3m17 Charming The Pziiffelback
***3m18 See You Tomorrow
**3m18 See You Tomorrow
*3m18 See You Tomorrow
3m18 See You Tomorrow
***3m20 Test Drive
**3m20 Test Drive
*3m20 Test Drive
3m20 Test Drive
***3m21[30] Not So Fireproof
**3m21[30] Not So Fireproof
*3m21[30] Not So Fireproof
3m21[30] Not So Fireproof
***3m22 This Time For Sure
**3m22 This Time For Sure
*3m22 This Time For Sure
3m22 This Time For Sure
***3m23 Astrid Finds Toothless
**3m23 Astrid Finds Toothless
*3m23 Astrid Finds Toothless
3m23 Astrid Finds Toothless
***3m24 Astrid Goes For A Spin
**3m24 Astrid Goes For A Spin
*3m24 Astrid Goes For A Spin
3m24 Astrid Goes For A Spin
3m25 Romantic Flight
***3m26b[23] Dragon's Den
**3m26b[23] Dragon's Den
*3m26b[23] Dragon's Den
3m26b[23] Dragon's Den
***3m26c Let's Find Dad
**3m26c Let's Find Dad
*3m26c Let's Find Dad
3m26c Let's Find Dad
***4m27-28 Kill Ring/Stop The Fight
**4m27-28 Kill Ring/Stop The Fight
*4m27-28 Kill Ring/Stop The Fight
4m27-28 Kill Ring/Stop The Fight
***4m30[11] Not A Viking
**4m30[11] Not A Viking
*4m30[11] Not A Viking
4m30[11] Not A Viking
4m31[-31] Ready/Confront
***4m31[48-95] Ready/Confront
**4m31[48-95] Ready/Confront
*4m31[48-95] Ready/Confront
4m31[48-95] Ready/Confront
***4m33-34[-26] Relax/Stroke/Hell
**4m33-34[-26] Relax/Stroke/Hell
*4m33-34[-26] Relax/Stroke/Hell
4m33-34[-26] Relax/Stroke/Hell
***4m35-37 Over/Less Okay
**4m35-37 Over/Less Okay
*4m35-37 Over/Less Okay
4m35-37 Over/Less Okay
4m38 Wings
***5m39 Counter Attack
**5m39 Counter Attack
*5m39 Counter Attack
5m39 Counter Attack
***5m40 Where's Hiccup?
**5m40 Where's Hiccup?
*5m40 Where's Hiccup?
5m40 Where's Hiccup?
**5m41[-67] Coming Back Around
*5m41[-67] Coming Back Around
5m41[-67] Coming Back Around
Jónsi: Sticks & Stones
5m41[67] Coming Back Around
1m2[-36] This Is Berk
2m14[56] Forbidden Friendship
3m24 Astrid Goes For A Spin
3m25 Romantic Flight